亲爱的  我们是在车里
We're in the car, honey.
我们要去医院做检查
We're going to the hospital for tests.
我们这是在医院
We're in the hospital.
现在去医生的办公室
We're going to the doctor's office.
你能告诉我这是什么吗
Can you tell me what this is called?
你用它弄出里面的食物
You use it to get food from inside.
对  但它叫什么
Yes, but what's it called?
是炒菜铲吗
Is it a spatula?
-不是  -很好
- No. - Good.
是开罐器吗
Is it a can opener?
不  它是...
No, it's...
是...
It's..
你故意想让我出丑
You're trying to make me look stupid.
你去死吧
You can go to hell!
你怎么不自杀呢
Why don't you kill yourself?
安德鲁
Andres.
没事的
It's okay.
你在这啊
There she is.
我在这
Here I am.
来  坐下吧
Here, come on.
你还得再回答几个问题
You just need to answer a few more questions.
然后我们就能回家  吃中午饭  好吗
Then we're going home. We'll have lunch, okay?
好的
Okay.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
我有阿尔茨海默病
I have Alzheimer's.
我知道
I know.
他情绪变化很快  但...
The mood swings come on quickly, but...
还是能控制住的
It's under control.
别担心  事实上他很适合这次药物试验
Don't worry. He's actually perfect for the drug trial.
谢天谢地
Thank god.
我们下周就可以开始
We can start as soon as next week.
安德鲁
Andres.
天啊
Oh, my god!
安德鲁
Andres...
总监：
zlean
家族遗传性阿尔茨海默病早期
Early onset familial Alzheimer's.
有巴西血统
Brazilian descent.
血生化检查显示氨含量很高
Blood chemistry showed high ammonia.
直到急诊室给他用上止吐药  才停止呕吐
Vomiting stopped after the E.R. put him on antiemetics.
最近有什么健康问题吗
Any recent health issues?
他几周前嗓子有点疼
Just a sore throat a few weeks ago.
他的病到什么程度了
How advanced is he?
可能到要静脉输营养液了
Could be hyperalimentation.
他病得挺严重  但还不用输营养液
Advanced enough, but no IV feedings.
他妻子关了鲜花公司
The wife shut down a floral company
待在家里照顾他
to stay home and feed him
这四年里  每一顿饭都是她妻子做的
every meal he's had in the last four years.
我们接这个病例是不是因为
Do we owe this case to your guilt
你对忽视自己健忘妈妈的愧疚感啊
at having ignored your own forgetful mommy?
我对我妈的内疚让我能忍受我爸
My guilt over my mom is why I put up with my dad.
你接这个病例是因为我们正在进行
You're taking this case because we're running
一个治疗二期阿尔茨海默病的新药试验
a phase-two trial on an Alzheimer's drug.
所以你是找不到足够的老实验豚鼠
You couldn't round up enough doddering old guinea pigs.
非得要我们治好这一只啊
You need us to fix this little piggy?
你最好坐下吧
Might like to sit in.
尤其你现在少一个组员
Especially since you're short a team member.
你是说陶博吗  就在我包里呢
You mean Taub? Got him in here.
他今天请假了  他女儿病了
He asked for a personal day. His daughter's sick.
这不就是有两个女儿的意义吗
Isn't that the point of having a spare?
我拒绝了他的请求
I denied his request.
而我已经批准了
After I'd already approved it,
你也知道因为我给你发了一份备忘录
which you knew because I sent you a memo.
亚当斯医生
Dr. Adams,
在你椅子底下
taped under your chair
粘着一张卡片
is an index card.
你能念一下吗
Would you read it, please?
"周三  下午2:43
"Wednesday, 2:43 P.M.,
一个黑人卒子自以为他是黑人国王
"A black pawn will believe he's the black king
并且企图去干掉
"and attempt to capture the...
诊断科的白人头目"
white head of diagnostics."
-现在是周五上午10:15  -见鬼
- It's 10:15 on Friday. - Damn it.
重点是我知道这事会发生
Look, the point is I saw this coming.
福曼医生之前就看我不顺眼
Dr. Foreman and I did not always see eye-to-eye,
但他从来没有权力来管我
but he never had the power to overrule me.
现在他有了这样的权力
Now that he has the power, he won't be able
就无法抵抗去使用这权力的欲望
to resist the temptation to use it.
权力越大  事情就要做得更细致
With great power comes great micromanaging.
还有你背心挺好看的
And great vests.
我知道你是比我更优秀的诊断医生
I know you're the better diagnostician.
我不会干扰你  我只是来帮忙的
I'm not gonna interfere. I'm only here to help.
可能是急性上消化道出血所致过性氮质血症
Could be transient nitrogen load from a G.I. bleed.
那样的话呕吐应该是持久性的
Not if the vomiting's persistent.
这我们就不知道了
Which we won't know,
因为急诊室给他用上了止吐药
because the E.R. put him on antiemetics.
给他停用
Take him off.
等等  他都快把肠子吐出来了
Wait. He's puking his guts out.
会有要留置胃管的风险
We'd risk aspiration.
我只是不同意你  没有压制你的意思
I'm just disagreeing, not overruling.
你能加入我真高兴
So glad you're on board.
给他停用止吐药
Take him off antiemetics,
给他做胃镜  找找出血点
do an upper endoscopy to check for bleeds.
有可能是膀胱炎
It could be a bladder infection.
我们要做一次妊娠试验
We'll run a pregnancy test.
我没有怀孕
Oh, I'm not pregnant.
任何一种避孕措施都有可能失效
Any type of birth control can fail.
我的不会
Not mine.
抱歉  你说你已经结婚了
Oh, I'm sorry. You said you were married.
对  还很幸福
Yeah, happily.
那挺好
That's okay.
结婚时间长了  性致不高很正常
Sex can wane in any marriage over time.
不  不  我们从没做过爱
No, no. We've never had sex.
我们接吻  抚摸
Oh, we kiss and cuddle,
但我们两人对做爱都没什么兴趣
but neither one of us is interested in sex.
你们俩  都是禁欲主义者吗
You're...both celibate.
不  我们俩都不是
No, neither of us.
禁欲主义是一个选择  这是我们的性取向
Celibacy is a choice. This is our orientation.
我们是无性恋者
We're asexual.
我有点不确定该选哪一项了
Not quite sure what box to check here.
你是在犯错
You're making a mistake.
如果我有能否决他的权力
If I had the power to veto him,
想到我这些年来受的气
given all the crap I've put up with over the years,
我可不知道我能否公正的使用这权力
don't know if I could use it objectively.
我有这权力  我能公正  也是这么做的
I do, I can, I have.
如果你不掺和  也许能好办些
Might be easier if you'd stay out of the room.
我以为他这周能有些
I thought it'd be different
不同
this week.
本来要和他的保释官
Supposed to talk to his P.O.
谈谈提前移除他脚踝监视器的事
about getting his ankle monitor off early.
你是说他对你的态度应该有所变化吗
You're saying he should defer to you?
不  我的意思是他的所作所为好像不理性
No, I'm just saying what he's doing doesn't seem rational,
这就让我觉得  他会这么做
which makes me think it's rational
是出于某种我没想到的原因
in a way I'm not privy to.
他总是胸有成竹
He always has a plan.
而且他总是喜欢自我毁灭
And he's always self-destructive.
他也许这会正在朝自己的脚踝开枪呢
He may just be shooting himself in the ankle.
你在普林斯顿普雷斯波罗教学医院
今天是星期五
我知道这对你有些陌生
I know it feels strange.
奇斯医生正在检查你的喉咙
Dr. Chase is just looking in your throat.
我们在医院
We're in the hospital.
你没事的
You're fine.
那奖杯真不错  安德鲁
That's a pretty nice trophy, there, Andres.
他教青少年足球
He coached youth soccer.
将一个零比六惨败的队伍
Took a team that was 0-6
一直带到了州际决赛
all the way to the state finals at long branch.
谢谢你们在这里做检查
Hey, thanks for doing this in here.
换房间会让他迷糊
Switching rooms can be very disorienting.
你将他照顾得很好
You take very good care of him.
我爱他  无论疾病或健康都伴他左右
I love him. Sickness and health, right?
食管上段未见异常
Upper esophagus is clear.
进镜至食管胃连接部
Moving on to the G.E. Junction.
-你好  -抱歉
- Hey. - I'm sorry.
检查过程中只允许家人在场
Family members only during procedures.
这个  我  我待外面吧
I'll-- I'll be outside.
不用  拜托了
Oh, no. Please,
没关系的
It's okay.
约瑟夫有时会帮我照顾我老公
Joseph helps me with my husband sometimes.
他是好朋友
He's a good friend.
也就是说不是家人
Which means not family.
稍等  我们还有一会儿才结束
Wait, we're gonna be here a while.
你带约瑟夫去访客等候区吧
Why don't you show Joseph where the visitor's lounge is?
好吧
Okay.
怎么了
What?
你还真是没有眼力劲啊
Surprised you didn't go into the diplomatic corps.
哦  你以为他们
Oh, you think they're...
没有  如果他们有奸情的话
No, if they're having sex,
也就是生理需求而已
it's probably with their genitals.
贲门撕裂综合征样的撕裂
Mallory-weiss tear.
一定是呕吐撕裂了黏膜
Vomiting must have torn the lining.
只有近百分之一的人
You know that close to 1% of the population
是无性恋者
identifies as asexual?
哥们你真得找个人发泄下了
We really gotta get you laid.
如果一定要我出马的话  也行吧
If I have to plough that furrow myself, so be it.
我有个无性恋病人
I have a patient who's asexual.
她是一池子海藻吗
Is she a giant pool of algae?
这是种合理的性取向
It's a valid sexual orientation.
至少这篇文章是这么说的
According to this article, at least.
没错  我想我也读过
Yeah, I think I read that too.
是丑毙了周刊吗
Is that fugliness weekly?
她长得挺好看
She's perfectly fine-looking.
结婚十年婚姻美满
Happily married for ten years.
老公绝对是个同性恋吧
To a guy who loves penis enough for the both of them.
他也是无性恋者
He's asexual too.
我给她做了全套检查
Ran a complete physical on her.
除了膀胱炎一切正常
Nothing wrong except a common bladder infection.
赌一百  我可以找出
100 bucks says I can find a medical reason
她不做爱的医学原因
why she doesn't want to have sex.
你疯了吧
You're out of your mind
我怎么可能让你接近我的病人
if you think I'm letting you anywhere near my patient.
好吧  我不靠近她
Fine. I won't go near her.
把她的病例
Just give me her file
和剩下的血液样本给我就好
and any blood samples you have left over.
不能有任何形式的接触
No contact, whatsoever.
你和她说话  这个赌就无效
You talk to her, the bet is void.
不接触
No contact.
正合我意
Plays to my strengths anyway.
豪斯  现在不是时候
Right now's not a good time, House.
对院长来说  确实不是时候
Not for the Dean of Medicine.
但若你是我团队的一员  就正是时候
But it's a perfect time if you're a member of my team.
你到底是什么身份
Which one are you?
胃镜有什么发现吗
What did the endoscopy show?
没有发现溃疡及血凝块
No signs of ulcers or blockages.
但在食管以下发现一处黏膜撕裂
But you found a tear just below the esophagus.
能解释出血
Explains the bleeding.
但解释不了为什么他吐得这么厉害
Doesn't explain why he vomited so hard
以至于撕裂了内脏
he ripped his insides.
他肝的转氨酶轻度升高
His liver enzymes are slightly elevated.
胆结石肯
Gallstones could've--
但没有听他说疼啊
No complaints of pain.
脂肪肝可致谷丙谷草转氨酶升高
Steatohepatitis would make his AST and ALT levels rise.
你是说他患有脂肪肝
Are you calling his liver fat?
给他服用他汀类药物并给他做组织活检
Start the patient on statins, and do a biopsy to confirm.
把他弄晕
And knock him out.
我听说他不好伺候
I've heard he's a wiggler.
不需要这么做
There's no need to put him under.
我们可以通过超声波确诊脂肪肝
We can confirm fatty liver with an ultrasound.
是我根据观察提的建议
Just making an observation.
很好
Well done.
作为我团队的一员
Now, as a member of my team,
你可以做同样有效的观察
you can make the equally-useful observations
天空很蓝  我穿着裤子
that the sky is blue, I'm wearing pants,
还有我忽略你的第一个观察
and I'm ignoring your first observation.
我就知道
Of course.
等等
Wait.
来了吧
And there it is.
你想打击我的自信心
You're trying to screw with my confidence.
如果我想那么干的话
Well, if I wanted to do that,
我会告诉你护士有多讨厌你
I'd tell you how much the nurses hate you.
你想让我把自己当成你的狗腿子
You're trying to get me to define myself as a subordinate
对你的行为不做干涉
to keep me from ever intervening,
即使干涉你的行为是我的职责所在
even if it's fully in the scope of my duties.
就像现在这样
Like now.
这与诊断没有关系
This isn't about diagnostics,
但关系到病人的安危
it's about what's safe for the patient.
做超声波
Do the ultrasound.
这就去做超声波
Ultrasound it is.
护士们都爱你
And the nurses love you.
不要以为我不知道  豪斯让你们忽视我
You don't think I knew House was gonna tell you
不去做超声波检查
to ignore me and not do the ultrasound?
这可是台超声波仪器
This is an ultrasound machine.
可以打着超声波的幌子做组织活检
Which you're gonna use to do an ultrasound-guided biopsy.
这里可能还藏着个活检盒子呢
Probably got a kit stashed here...
"黑人版卡迪会将整个下午
"Cuddy dark will waste his afternoon
浪费在阴谋论上"
chasing conspiracy theories."
他已经成为你肚子里的蛔虫了
You're letting him get inside your head.
他可是能整出很大的破坏哦
He could do a lot of damage in there.
奇斯医生
Dr. Chase.
他又开始呕吐了
He started vomiting again.
这就是我们停止给他服用止吐剂的原因
This is why we stopped the antiemetics.
我们要看看这是不是个症状
We needed to see if it was still a symptom.
好的
Okay.
给你  你要这个吗
Here, you want this?
把手拿开
Get your hands off me.
你想要控制我
You're taking my head.
没事的  安德鲁
It's okay, Andres.
你在医院里
You're in the hospital.
给你
Here.
-10毫克安定  -已经用上了
- 10 milligrams of diazepam! - Already on it.
我没事  我真的没事
I'm fine. I'm fine.
我没事
I'm all right.
福曼
Foreman.
他开始尿血了
Blood in his urine.
给他服用止吐剂  加大镇定剂用量
Resume the antiemetics, and increase the sedation.
他真的对她动手了
He really went after her.
可能是他发现了她的奸情
Maybe he found out about her "Good friend."
这只是妄想型愤怒  阿尔茨海默的典型症状
It was just paranoid rage, typical of Alzheimer's.
他们又不一定一起睡了
We don't even know if they were sleeping together.
几小时前你还很肯定呢
A few hours ago you were sure.
这很重要吗
And that's significant why?
抱歉  只有出血和医疗有关
Sorry. Only the bleeding's medically relevant.
不是  我说的不是这个
No, I wasn't being rhetorical.
即便他们一起睡了
If they are sleeping together,
我们为何要反对呢
why do we disapprove?
你赞成不忠吗
You're pro-infidelity?
她又没有结婚
She's not married.
如果结婚是给人喂饭擦身
If marriage is feeding and cleaning someone
谈话的内容也只是重复些简单的指令
and limiting conversation to repeating a few simple commands,
那我早就和我的宠物老鼠结婚了
then I was married to my pet rat.
好多人都欠我结婚贺礼呢
And a lot of people owe me wedding gifts.
走起来  走起来
And we're walking, we're walking.
不管你另一半生多严重的病
I don't care how sick your spouse gets,
你不能抛弃对方
you don't jump ship.
阿尔茨海默不同
Alzheimer's is different.
她都无法和他探讨问题
She can't share her problems with him,
或者计划将来
or plan for the future.
娶她的那个男人已经不存在了
The man she married no longer exists.
他在的  就在那具身体里
Yes, he does. He's in there.
不然当初怎么会结婚
This is why you get married.
离婚女人对离婚男人如是说
Said the divorced woman to the divorced man.
我问心无愧
I didn't jump ship.
我前夫的出轨  葬送了我们的婚姻
My husband sank it when he cheated on me.
承诺是无条件的
Commitment's not conditional.
她还留在他身边  知道这点就足够了
She is there for him in the only way that matters now.
她放弃她的生活去照料他
She gave up her life to take care of him.
说明她是白痴
Which proves she's an idiot.
如果她有点脑子  就会把他扔疗养院了
If she had any sense, she'd have stuck him in a facility
然后跳上那艘奇怪的...
and jumped on that strange--
福曼医生
Dr. Foreman.
我们刚正找你呢
We were just looking for you.
关于止吐剂我是对的
I was right about the antiemetics.
如我所说  如果你没有停用
If you kept him on them like I said,
他就不会这么暴躁  揍他的妻子
he wouldn't have gotten agitated and punched his wife.
可不  我们又回到我那
Yes, we're back to my supposed diabolical plan
为动摇你信心而设的恶毒计划
to shake your confidence.
这样说吧
Let's see if this helps.
如果把你当作一个队员
If you're speaking as a team member,
我会说你是个白痴
then I'd say you're a moron.
因为让他停用止吐剂
Because taking him off the antiemetics
为我们的诊断提供了重要的信息
gave us crucial diagnostic information.
如果把你当做院长
If you're speaking as Dean of Medicine,
我会说你是个白痴
then I'd say you're a moron.
你事无巨细式的管理  让我们做不了活检
'cause your micromanaging kept us from doing a biopsy.
如果我们做了  病人几小时前就会被麻醉
If we had, the patient would have been anesthetized hours ago,
那就不会把她揍得鼻青脸肿的
thus unable to go all chris brown on her ass.
除非你确实
Unless one of your index cards
预见到他会揍他老婆
actually predicted the guy was gonna punch his wife,
不然你说的全都是马后炮
everything you're saying is post hoc rationalization.
朴克医生
Dr. Park,
你能把手伸到椅子下面吗
Would you please reach under that chair?
"病人会揍他妻子"
"The patient will punch his wife."
你肯定是在事后写的
You clearly wrote that after the fact.
亚当斯医生
Dr. Adams,
你能把手伸到我裤子里吗
Would you please reach into my pants?
"黑鬼医生
"Dr. Blackenshmurtz
会说我是在事后写的"
will accuse me of writing about the punch after the fact."
现在  看
Now, look.
这是我拿着一张报纸的照片
Here's a photograph of me holding a newspaper.
上周二的
Dated last tuesday.
你说我怎么可能在事后做到呢
Now, how could I have gotten my hands on that?
说完了吗
You done?
横纹肌溶解症与呕吐
Rhabdomyolysis fits the vomiting,
尿色异常  肾衰竭等相符
pigmenturia, and renal failure.
肌肉没有出现问题  尿中无肌红蛋白
No muscle symptoms, and urine had no myoglobin.
血栓性血小板减少性紫癜符合
TTP fits, though.
开始做血浆置换
Start him on plasmapheresis.
除非...
Unless...
除非我还得说  "妈  可以吗"
Unless I need to say, "Mother, may I?"
妈是一个简称
And mother is an abbreviation.
新鲜血浆可置换出那些
Fresh plasma will replace the damaged red blood cells
会引起肾小管堵塞的受损细胞
that are clogging his kidneys.
听上去应该没什么问题
That sounds hopeful.
你感觉怎么样
How is that feeling?
我从来没被人照着脸打过
I've never been hit in the eye before.
感觉真不怎么样
I feel kinda badass.
也许你该走了
I think maybe you should go.
我没关系的
I'm fine. Okay?
明天见
See you tomorrow.
好
Okay.
我们没有搞婚外恋
We're not having an affair.
这和我无关
It's none of my business.
我是说  不算是
I mean, not-- not really.
因为什么都没有发生过
'cause nothing's happened.
我们谈很多...
We've talked about it a lot, and...
一个人这样照顾他实在太困难了
It's just really hard doing this by myself.
你最后一次睡个安稳觉是什么时候
When's the last time you had a full night's sleep?
我不知道  三年前吧
I don't know. Three years.
在这里你没法休息
You're not going to get any rest here.
病人并非是
People who are sick are not the only ones
唯一需要被照顾的人
who need to be taken care of.
为什么奇斯不用来
Why doesn't Chase have to be here?
你觉得他对不想性交的女人
You think he knows anything about women
会有了解吗
who don't want to have sex?
荷尔蒙水平正常
Hormone levels are normal.
这个女人看上去非常健康
This woman seems perfectly healthy.
她说她是无性恋又怎么样
What does it matter if she says she's asexual?
这是我们人类的本能
It's the fundamental drive of our species.
性是健康的
Sex is healthy.
性高潮给大脑供氧
Orgasms oxygenate the brain,
照亮30个不同的区域
lighting up over 30 different areas
还能让我们忘记苏西·库柏有多无聊
and making us forget how boring Susie Cooper is.
最后一条可能不是普遍规律
That last one may not be universal.
会不会是脊椎受损
How about damage to her spinal cord
阻滞信号传输到她的生殖器
blocking the signals from her genitals?
性冲动是大脑控制的
Sex drive is in the brain.
我认为可能是心理上的亲密问题
I suppose it could be psychological intimacy issues
由童年的虐待引起的
caused by childhood abuse.
过去十年  她和同一个男人
She's been sharing a toilet with the same guy
共用一个厕所
for the last ten years.
那不一样
That's not the same.
性让人释放催产素
Sex releases oxytocin.
这是人类情感的神经化学基础
It's the neurochemical basis for bonding.
这就是为什么男人都和他的右手结婚
And that's why men always marry their right hands.
对女孩来说不一样
It's different for girls.
不  一样
No it's not.
我上过30个男人
I've tapped over 30 guys
大部分我都不想再见第二次
and never wanted to see most of them again.
我住在犹太兄弟会旁边
I live next to a Jewish frat.
我们离题十万八千里了  不过请继续
We are veering wildly off track. Please continue.
这个女人脱离性  可能更好过一点
This woman's life is probably better off without sex.
可以消除她的不安
Eliminates most of her insecurity,
她对商品广告基本不感冒
She's immune to most advertising.
而且还能与男士们保持种开诚布公的关系
And can have honest relationships with men.
这种人凤毛麟角
Not a lot of them.
该做的检测都做过了  都没有问题
We've run every test and ruled out all the options.
你还是接受事实吧
You're gonna have to accept
她就是没性趣
she just doesn't want sex.
没有性事的人有很多种
Lots of people don't have sex.
但是没有性趣的人
The only people who don't want it.
要么是病了  要么死了  要么是在说谎
Are either sick, dead, or lying.
可能她是在说谎吧
So maybe she's lying.
你觉得她在外面还有个相好
You think she's had a boyfriend on the side?
有十年了吧
For ten years?
这种关系能维持这么长时间  不太可能
Sticking around the whole time? Doesn't make sense.
怎么说呢
What does...
有30个吗
30?
我骗他的
Everybody lies.
超过还是不到30
Higher or lower?
我采纳了你的建议  回去睡了觉
Followed your advice and took the night off.
你脸色看上去好点了
Seems to have done you some good.
我丈夫呢
Where's my husband?
他人不在医院里
He's not in the hospital.
他就这么走出去了吗
So he just walked out?
所有的当班护士
All of the shift nurses
都被重急症忙得不可开交
had their hands full with a double code.
真是合情合理的解释啊
Perfectly reasonable explaination.
这事儿我经历得多了去了
Same thing happened to me.
常常几天找不到门钥匙
Couldn't find my keys for days.
我们已经报警了
The police have been notified.
我也派人去找了
I have staff searching.
是你让我放心回家的
You told me it was okay to leave.
对不起
I'm sorry.
他有阿尔茨海默病啊
He has Alzheimer's!
外面冰天雪地的  他又得了病
It's freezing outside, and he's sick!
你们甚至连他得的什么病都不知道  是不是
I mean, you don't even know what it is yet, do you?
血浆除去法还没见效
The plasmapheresis hasn't had time to work,
血栓性血小减少性紫癜最有可能
but TTP is our most likely...
好了  我得出去找他
Okay, I'm just... I have to go look for him.
别犯浑
Hey, don't be an ass.
你看不出她很担心吗
Can't you see she's upset?
不对  她这是内疚
No, she's guilty.
因为她非但没有陪在丈夫床前
Cause instead of being at her husband's side,
还和你享受了床第之欢
she was under you.
你  你
Okay, that's...
对  对  对
Yeah, yeah, yeah...
他骂过我混蛋了
He already said I was an ass.
我个人而言  为你的决定击节叫好
Personally, I applaud your decision
你能放下这个负担
to step down off your cross
继续你自己的生活
and get on with your life,
但是你这种不合时宜的愧疚感影响了你的思维
But your misplaced guilt is shutting down your brain.
你给我坐下来  集中精神  回答我们的问题
We need you to sit, focus, and answer our questions.
早上六点
At 6 a.m.
你丈夫醒来
the patient wakes up,
他看见的第一样事物是...
and the first thing he sees...
在感到困惑时
In moments of confusion,
阿尔茨海默病患者会回到以前的生活习惯
Alzheimer's patients regress to old routines.
这么说来  周六早晨你丈夫会干些什么事
So what would your husband do on a Saturday morning?
什么都不干  在家待着
Nothing. Be at home.
那么一年前  或者五年前  十年前呢
What about a year ago? Or five years? Ten?
我不知道
I don't know, um, he...
他练过马拉松
He trained for a marathon once.
训练足球队  上烹饪课
Soccer practice. We took a cooking class.
你说过的那个足球奖杯
That soccer trophy you were telling me about.
不见了
It's gone.
他在哪里训练
Where was practice?
离这里不远  在切斯特菲尔德
It was close to here, on Chesterfield.
他过来  等待训练开始
Okay, he comes, he thinks he's waiting for practice.
他要找个避风的地方
He'd want to get out of the wind.
有什么地方他能看到达到球场的队员吗
What's somewhere he could see the kids arrive?
那边
There.
他在这里
Over here.
数三下  一  二  三
On three. One, two, three.
没脉搏
Nothing.
这么冷的环境下还有一线生机
Not dead until he's warm and dead.
把他送去重症监护室
Get him to the ICU.
给他接上体外循环
Start him on extracorporeal circulation.
那样他的体温回升得太快
That'll raise his temperature too quickly,
会导致酸中毒
It'll cause acidosis.
我们有能力处理他的代谢障碍
We can deal with his metabolism crashing,
但是如果动作太慢就无法恢复脑部损伤了
we can't reverse brain damage if we go too slowly.
不管怎么样
Either way,
如果不把他的体温升到35摄氏度
we don't get his temperature above 95,
就没什么戏了
it's not going to matter.
多通道加温灌洗更加安全
Multiple warm lavage is safer.
按豪斯说的做
Do what House says.
他没有心跳也没有呼吸
He has no heartbeat, and he's not breathing.
这还不算死亡吗
How can he not be dead?
人体在低温时会自动降低代谢速度
The body slows down when it cools,
但是并不会完全停止
but it doesn't fully stop.
我们从体外给他的血液加温
We're warming his blood outside of his body,
然后输回体内
then putting it back.
可以把他的体温升到正常
It'll raise his temperature enough
然后他的心脏就会自然开始跳动
that his heart should naturally start.
然后我们可以用电击使其回归到正常节律
Then we can shock it back into rhythm.
如果心脏不跳呢
And if it doesn't start?
那我们也无能为力了
Then there's nothing we can do.
你觉得他有可能知道自己在干什么吗
You think it's possible he knew what he was doing?
比如说他是否知道自己拖累了妻子
Like some part of him gets what he's putting his wife through,
-所以他试图  -自杀吗
- So he tried to...  - Kill himself?
换了我我就一死了之
It's what I'd do if I were him.
至少我希望我能死成
At least I wish I would.
我想说的是逃避
I meant run away.
你觉得如果对爱你的人来说
You think you should kill yourself
你变成了种负担  你就会自寻短见吗
if you become a burden to the people who love you?
如果我真心喜欢对方  那么...
If you really love them back, then...
我会的
Yes.
你真悲观
That's really dark.
是你太天真
It's not naive.
我相信换了别人
I just believe people are capable
应该能比你处理得好
of more than you do, apparently.
他脑部活动恢复了
We've got brain activity.
体温34度不到
Temp's at 93.
他的心脏应该快开始跳了
His heart should start soon.
我父亲丢下我一个人
My dad left me alone
照顾我酗酒的老妈
to care for my alcoholic mom
抚养我妹妹
and raise my baby sister.
我那时也还是个孩子
I was just a teenager.
我一半时间花在换尿布上
I spent half my time changing diapers
还有一半时间擦洗我妈的呕吐物
and the other half cleaning up my mom's vomit.
但是你为她们所做的
But it must've been important
对她们而言应该是意义重大吧
that you stayed for both of them.
几年后我妈死了
Mom died after a few years.
那过程痛苦得惨不忍睹
It was ugly and painful,
她至死  我都对她怀恨在心
and she went with me hating her.
我妹妹最后也开始酗酒  毁了大好年华
My sister ended up drinking half of her life away.
她恨我没有能够帮助她
And hating me because I couldn't help.
我妈走了之后  我无依无靠
After mom, I had nothing left.
我是否愿意她用枪了结生命而不是靠酒精慢性自杀
So do I wish mom had used a gun instead of a bottle?
我愿意
Yes.
我不知道有这事
I... I didn't know.
所以我才告诉你
That's why I told you.
心室纤颤
Ventricular fibrillation.
300毫克胺碘酮
300 milligrams amiodarone.
小心
Careful.
我们将他的心跳节律恢复之后
Once we establish rhythm,
任何不当的移动都可能导致他发生心室纤颤
any accidental movement could crash him back into v-fib.
离手
Clear.
我们还有很长的路要走
We still have a long way to go.
低温可以保护大脑
Cold can be protective to the brain,
但仍有脑损伤的可能
but there is a possibility of damage.
我们还需要确诊并治疗
We also need to confirm and treat
他的原发疾病
whatever's making him sick.
我得去做一套全面常规检查
I just gotta do a standard battery of tests.
验血验尿以及脑电图
Blood, urine, EEG...
打一针免费的流感疫苗要这么麻烦吗
Is that really necessary for a free flu shot?
不好意思
Excuse me.
我得去对付某个惊慌失措的人
I have to deal with someone who's having a panic attack.
我特别强调过
I specifically said
如果你联系病人我们的赌就无效
the bet was off if you contacted the patient.
确实
Exactly.
对于病人的丈夫你可什么都没说过
Never said anything about the patient's husband.
我们的赌注是为她不进行性生活找到医学原因
The deal was a medical reason why she doesn't have sex.
我承认我黔驴技穷了
I admit I was stuck,
直到我意识到有病的不是她而是她丈夫
until I realized the medical issue was not hers but his.
她是通过撒谎来作为弥补
She's lying to compensate.
这是个古老的故事了
It's a tale as old as time.
男孩遇见了女孩  女孩爱上了男孩
Boy meets girl, girl falls for boy,
男孩说我没有性欲  女孩说我也是
Boy says, "I'm asexual." Girl says, "Yeah, me too."
你这扭曲的逻辑也无法掩盖
Your twisted logic can't hide the fact
欺骗病人进行测试是不道德的
that tricking a patient into being tested
这个事实
is completely unethical.
算了吧
Come on.
你不认为她理应知道为什么
Don't you think she deserves to know why her husband
她丈夫不愿在厨柜上把她推倒吗
won't bend her over the kitchen counter?
你就喜欢这种破事
You love all that caring crap.
你这么做不是因为良心发现
You're not doing this out of the kindness of your heart.
甚至不是出于对医学的好奇
You're not even doing this out of medical curiosity.
我觉得我已经说得很清楚我这么做是为了钱
I thought I made it clear I'm doing it for the cash.
那两个人很幸福
Two people are happy,
而你的本能就是去破坏它
and your natural impulse is to destroy it.
你怎么知道她幸福呢
How do you know she's happy?
她告诉你的吗
Did she tell you?
不  她的幸福溢于言表
No, chirping birds flew out of her butt carrying a banner.
好吧  我承认我的本能
All right, I admit that my natural impulse
是质疑声称幸福的人们
is to doubt peoples' claims to happiness,
而你就是迫切希望别人幸福
but yours is to be a sucker for them.
你说咱俩谁更糟
You tell me which one's worse.
他刚才睁眼了
He just opened his eyes a little while ago.
他的心跳很正常
His heartbeat's doing well,
体温也稳定了
and his body temperature is stabilized.
你在这
There he is.
我觉得很热
Me sinto quente.
他说得是葡萄牙语吗
Is that Portuguese?
是的
Yeah.
亲爱的我听不懂
Honey, I don't understand.
我觉得很热
Me sinto quente.
他在说什么
What's he saying?
我不知道
I don't know.
我们结婚时我想学来着
I tried to learn when we got married,
但是我...
but I just--
没关系  会好的
It's okay. It's okay.
他的体温正在上升
His body temperature is rising.
已经高于正常值了
It's above normal.
等等  我记得
Wait, I thought--
我记得你刚说过他的情况稳定了
I thought you said it was stable.
为什么体温还在升高
Why is it still rising?
我不知道
I don't know.
呕吐  肝脏问题  肾脏问题现在又是发热
Vomiting, liver, kidneys, and now fever.
我不想告诉你该如何工作  福曼医生
I don't want to tell you how to do your job, Dr. Foreman,
因为告诉别人如何工作正是你的职责
since telling people how to do their job is your job,
不过如果你的不完善的入院看护程序
but when your less-than-competent administration of this hospital
影响到了写在我白板上的症状...
affects what's written on my whiteboard...
直入主题吧
Get to the point.
发热这个症状
The word "Fever."
可能是由于患者的病
could come from the patient's illness,
也有可能是由于你允许他
or it could come from the fact that you allowed him
漫步出医院并在冰天雪地上小憩了一会所致
to saunter out of your hospital and take a nap in the snow.
不可能是他在外面染上了某种病毒
Couldn't have caught a virus while he was outside.
发热来得太快了
Fever came on too fast.
体温过低可能导致细胞坏死
The hypothermia could've caused cell necrosis.
他出走前的诊断是血栓性血小板减少性紫癜
TTP was the diagnosis when he walked out.
发热温度有点高  但依然符合
Fever's a little high, but it still fits.
我们应该继续进行血浆除去法治疗
We should continue plasmapheresis.
我们漏掉了一个症状
We're missing symptoms.
我们应将加上失语和攻击性行为
We should add language loss and aggression.
我们还应该加上健忘吗
Should we also add forgetfulness?
-他患有阿尔茨海默病  -我们只是这么认为
- He's got Alzheimer's. - We've just been assuming.
因为患者的妻子
Because the patient's wife
说他出现这两个症状一年了
said he exhibited both for a year.
他以前从没打过她
He's never hit her before
或者突然不会说英语了
or lost all his English.
我们必须将他入院起的一切变化
We have to consider any change
都纳入考虑
since he's been admitted as relevant.
必须
Have to?
我是不是该再拿出一张卡片
Do I need to pull out another card?
病毒感染播散导致的脑炎
Disseminated viral infection with encephalitis.
患者几周前曾有过咽喉痛
Patient complained of a sore throat a few weeks ago.
给他用干扰素
Start him on interferon.
脑炎会使他的大脑肿胀
Encephalitis makes his brain swell,
这使他的症状很难
which causes symptoms that are
与阿尔茨海默病区别开
hard to distinguish from his Alzheimer's.
用了干扰素之后他应该又能说英语了
With the interferon his english should come back,
而攻击性行为也应该可以平静下来了
and the aggression should subside.
但你们并不确定
But you're not sure.
很遗憾我们也不知道
Unfortunately, no.
你们也不知道体温过低是否导致了脑损伤
And you're not sure if he has brain damage from being frozen.
那最好的情况就是
So best-case scenario,
我只是看到一眼他未来的样子
I've just had a glimpse into his future?
我没法再照顾他了
I can't take care of him anymore.
他的精神状态极有可能得到改善
Chances are his mental state will improve.
你可以有更多的时间和他在一起
You could get more time with him.
我们认识六个月就结婚了
We married six months after I met him.
一年以后他开始忘记事情
A year after that, he started forgetting things.
我陪伴患阿尔茨海默病的他
I've known my husband longer with his Alzheimer's
更久
than without.
了解犯病时的他
I've watched more of him disappear
更多
than I ever got to know.
我再也支撑不住了
I just can't do this anymore.
你输了
You lose.
血检显示泌乳刺激素水平过高
Blood work shows high levels of prolactin.
再加上轻微红绿混淆
Add that to some peripheral red-green confusion,
意味着我的钱  不好意思  是你的钱
puts my money-- excuse me, your money--
很快就会变成我的钱
soon to be my money
得利于他脑垂体旁的肿瘤
on a tumor near his pituitary.
可能他十几岁时就有了
Probably started growing in his early teens.
这不仅降低了他的性欲
Lowering his libido
还导致他勃起机能障碍
and causing erectile dysfunction.
经过一年的多巴胺受体激动剂治疗
A year on dopamine agonists,
他会和我们一样  痴迷性爱
And he'll be a sex-crazed creep just like the rest of us,
为苏西·库柏的手艺着迷
completely fascinated by Susie Cooper.
希望你能付我100美元纸钞
I'd prefer to be paid in a single $100 bill.
总想烧一张来点雪茄
Always wanted to use one to light a cigar.
我们好厉害  证明了他不是无性主义
Hooray for us. We disproved his asexuality.
很可能也毁掉了他的生活
We also probably ruined his life.
他会感谢我们
He'll thank us.
然后跑掉
Then he'll doze off,
过上几小时  再来感谢我们
and then in a couple hours, he'll thank us again.
这可能会毁掉他的自我认知
It could destroy his identity.
就好像告诉同性恋他其实是异性恋
It's like a gay person being told they're really straight.
那就别告诉他
So don't tell him.
一个人脑子里长了肿瘤而已
Yeah, why bother telling a guy
为什么偏要告诉他呢
he has a tumor growing in his head?
长到肿瘤从耳朵冒出来  他迟早会发现的
He'll notice it eventually, when it starts leaking out his ears.
这个肿瘤生长缓慢
It's a slow-growing tumor.
八成没到那时他就无聊而死了
He'll probably die of boredom long before that.
你总是这样
You always do this.
你...你每次一插手
You--you meddle
都让我进退两难
and force me into impossible situations.
你心里清楚得很  讲这个病例给我听
You knew the second you told me about this case
我必会插手
that I'd get involved.
你希望我插手
You wanted me to meddle.
因为不论你心中多么情愿相信
Because no matter how much you wanted
这纯洁的浪漫
to believe in this chaste romance,
其实你也不买账
you didn't buy it either.
豪斯的假释官发来的公文
Where's that petition House's P.O. sent over
关于摘掉追踪器的  在哪里
about getting his ankle monitor off?
在你桌上
On your desk.
你耍我
You played me.
大费周章全是为了你的追踪器
This whole thing was about your ankle monitor.
你并不是想打压我的自信
You weren't trying to undermine my confidence,
而是想让我信心膨胀
you were trying to inflate it.
你有意制造了与我的冲突
You manufactured conflict with me
一步步引我取胜
so eventually you could let me win.
你早就知道是脑炎  偏等我先说出来
You knew it was encephalitis, but you waited for me to say it.
因为你认为  等我自信膨胀起来
Because then with my ego boosted,
一定会高高兴兴替你取下追踪器
you thought I'd be in the mood to take off your monitor
因为我会自以为能够控制你了
Because I'd think I could control you.
你说对了  摘掉追踪器吧
You're right. Take off my monitor.
你看  这个计划的美妙之处就在于
See, the beauty of the plan
倘若它奏效  你会认为能够控制我
is that if it works, you think you can control me.
倘若失败了  又恰恰证明
If it fails, then you will actually have proven
你确实能够掌控我
that you can control me.
很天才的哟
It's pretty genius.
这是你练车的辅助轮
These are your training wheels.
如果你认为自己能够胜任
If you think you're up to this job,
是时候该拆掉了
it's time to lose them.
计划的收尾部分可能还需完善
Second half of my plan might need work.
心室纤颤  两次360焦除颤没能恢复节律
V-fib. Two rounds of 360 without establishing a rhythm.
等等  福曼医生
Wait, Dr. Foreman!
让开
Clear.
他没事了
He's back.
真希望这例阿尔茨海默病的试药
I sure hope this Alzheimer's drug trial
对本院大有助益
is worth a lot to this hospital,
我们投入这么多时间精力
'cause we're wasting a crap-load of time and manpower
却只能眼睁睁看着这男人脑萎缩
just to let this guy watch his mind shrivel
令他的妻子活在痛苦之中
and keep his wife miserable.
使用干扰素时出现心脏病发作
Heart attack while he was on interferon
排除了脑炎
rules out encephalitis,
但我仍认为我对神经症状的判断是正确的
but I still think I'm right about the neural symptoms.
很可能是无菌性脑膜炎
It's probably aseptic meningitis.
应该看得到脑膜刺激征
Would have seen meningial signs.
他的精神状况异常  所以也不见得
Given his abnormal mental status, not necessarily.
福曼医生
Dr. Foreman,
请你摸一下椅子下面好吗
Would you please reach under your chair?
只有一块嚼过的口香糖  纸片在哪里
There's just wet gum under here. Where's the card?
什么纸片
What card?
如果你有比无菌性脑膜炎更好的推测
I'm happy to leave if you have
我很乐意离开
a better theory than aseptic meningitis.
毒素
Toxins.
这家伙自己跑出去一次
This guy went on walkabout.
以前很可能也这么干过
chances are he's done it before.
家里的门都被他妻子上了锁
Wife keeps the doors on the house locked.
深更半夜乱撞
Plenty of nasty stuff to get into
很容易碰上有毒物质
during the middle of the night.
我们询问过中毒史
We asked about toxins on the history.
病人妻子说她很确定  为了他的安全
The wife said she was sure to clear the house
检查过家里
for her husband's safety.
我相信她成功了
I'm sure she succeeded.
她可是毒理学博士呢
She's a Ph.D in toxicology, right?
她以前是开花店的
She's an ex-florist.
去搜他们家  寻找有毒植物
Search the home for toxic plants,
溴代甲烷  所有的药品
methyl bromide, any medications.
停
Stop.
你的理论有缺陷  你关于脑炎的推测是错的
You're not infallible. You were wrong about encephalitis.
你现在的推测也不对
Just before you were.
做脑脊液检查
Run CSF tests.
查出脑膜炎的诱因
Find out what's causing the meningitis.
你说过不会否决我的诊断意见
You said you weren't gonna overrule me diagnostically.
你也说过我一定管不住自己
And you said I wouldn't be able to help it.
显然  这件事上你猜中了
Apparently, you were right about that one.
好吧
Fine.
我自己去查毒素
I'll look for toxins myself.
没有福曼的准许  你不能去他们的住处
You can't go to their house without Foreman's permission.
我不需要
Don't need it.
我去找楼上的毒理学博士谈谈
I'll talk to the toxicology Ph.D upstairs.
有从南美送来的礼物吗
What about gifts from South America?
有没有人送过水果或者蔬菜
Anyone send any fruits or vegetables?
我想应该没有  没有
I don't think so, no.
[葡萄牙语]
Barraco azul...
我需要你男朋友帮忙
I'm gonna need your boyfriend
收集你家里和住宅四周
to collect samples of plants
植物的样本  毒素是最有可能...
in and around your house. Toxins are the most...
[葡萄牙语]
Barraco azul...
- O que e isso? - Barraco azul?
等等  你听得懂他讲话
Wait, you understand him?
他在说什么
What's he saying?
他反复念叨"蓝窝棚"
He's--he's repeating, "Blue shack."
你知道是什么吗
You know what that is?
是会放农药的地方吗
Is it somewhere where pesticides may be kept?
那是我们第一次约会的地方
It's where we had our first date.
有没有清洁女工
Do you have a cleaning lady
可能会自带清洁用品的
who might bring her own supplies?
他在说什么
What's he saying?
他说什么与病情无关  我不关心
If it's not relevant to the case, I don't care.
你也不该在意
And neither should you.
求你了
Please.
这可能是我最后一次知道他的想法
This might be the last time I ever know what he's thinking.
当我第一眼见到她
When I saw her waiting...
在桌旁等我
waiting for me at the table...
她的双眼  她微笑的样子
The way her eyes looked when she smiled...
让我想要哭泣
I felt like crying.
我知道她就是我要娶的女人
I knew that she was the woman I wanted to marry.
每次见到她  我都会说
Every time I see her, I say...
[葡萄牙语]
La esta ela.
-就是她   -你在这啊
- There she is. - There she is.
他还记得
He's still in there.
她是谁
Quem e ela?
他说什么
What did he say?
他问你是谁
He asked who you were.
不是你想的那样
Don't get your hopes up.
让你男朋友把那些样本给我
Have your boyfriend give me those samples.
你怎么知道要去检查肿瘤
How'd you even know to look for a tumor?
豪斯医生发现你的血液里的激素水平异常
Well, Dr. House noticed hormone levels in your blood,
然后就咨询了我这个肿瘤医生
and consulted me as an oncologist.
别管怎么发现的  他们查出来了
Who cares how they found it, okay? They found it.
治疗有副作用吗
Are there any side effects to the treatment?
可能会产生恶心  眩晕
Some nausea, dizziness,
随着肿瘤缩小  还会发生一些行为改变
and as the tumor shrinks, there will be behavioral changes.
什么异常
Like what?
这个
Well...
这颗肿瘤影响了你的生理功能
The tumor interferes with certain natural systems.
降低性欲  导致勃起功能障碍
It lowers libido and causes erectile dysfunction.
你是说治疗会导致我性欲旺盛吗
Y-you mean the treatment will, m-make me want to have sex?
如果不治疗  会怎么样
Wh-what if I don't want the treatment?
我强烈建议你
I would strongly advise...
你脑部有肿瘤  必须得治疗
You have a brain tumor, okay? You have to have the treatment.
别说了  我了解自己
Okay, look, I know who I am, okay?
我不是那样的
And I'm not one of them.
我们会没事的  好吗
Hey, look, we'll adjust. Okay?
我们可以度过难关的
We can go through this together.
你是说做爱吗
You mean have sex?
不能让你那样
I can't make you do that.
也许情况不是那么糟
Maybe it won't be so bad.
会变得很糟糕
It'll be terrible.
其实挺有趣的
It's actually pretty fun.
就我记得而言
From what I remember.
-但是你说过  -我知道
- But you said that... - I know.
我想与子偕老
I know. I wanted to spend my life with you.
必然要做出一些牺牲
And I knew that meant making certain sacrifices.
但是女人也是有需要的
But a girl has needs.
你已经跌出美国新闻排行榜了
You dropped in the U.S. News rankings.
拉丰先生  恕我直言
With respect, Mr. Laffont,
那仅仅因为我们曾经暂时关闭了诊断部门
That's only because we temporarily shut down our diagnostics department.
现在又重新运作了
It's up and running again.
但我认为这是由于管理不善导致的
I'm actually concerned it might be Because of the change in management.
如果要我投资
If you want my money,
必须把未来五年计划报告交给我
I'll need to see a five-year plan.
我让你无聊了吗
Am I boring you?
没有没有  只是
No, no, I just...
那些花是上周的
Those flowers are from last week.
现在应该枯萎了啊
They should be dead by now.
不好意思
Excuse me?
抱歉  我得走了
Sorry. I have to go.
是雷依氏综合症
It's Reye's syndrome.
病人在住院前几个星期曾经咽喉痛
Patient had a sore throat a few weeks ago before he was admitted.
成年人中得雷依氏综合征是可能的
Reye's in adults is a reach.
要是服用了阿司匹林就不同了
Not if he took aspirin.
成人服用阿司匹林也是可能的
Aspirin in adults is a reach.
尤其被锁在一间都是药柜的屋子里
Especially in a house with locked medicine cabinets.
不是从药柜里拿的药
Wasn't in the medicine cabinet.
他的妻子以前经营一家花草公司
Wife used to run a floral company.
现在还在家里接一些单子
Still does a few orders from home.
她把阿司匹林压碎放在水里
She uses crushed aspirin in the water
延长花的保鲜期
to make the flowers last longer.
所以她的丈夫咽喉痛
So the husband has a sore throat,
然后在她不知道的情况  服用了阿司匹林
takes an aspirin without her knowing,
知道他喉咙痛后  又服用阿司匹林
Realizes he's got a sore throat, takes an aspirin,
知道他喉咙痛后
realizes he's got a sore throat...
你让我停我就停
Stop me whenever you like.
让奇斯给他上类固醇
Have Chase start him on steroids.
已经做了
Already did.
那为什么还告诉我
Then why're you telling me?
因为我想让你听听我的想法
'Cause I wanted you to hear it from me.
你在这啊
There she is.
我在这
Here I am.
你的眼睛
Your eye.
怎么了
What happened?
没事的
It's nothing I can't handle.
核磁共振确诊是巨大泌乳素瘤
MRI confirmed macroprolactinoma.
他在接受治疗
He's doing the treatment.
那妻子呢
And the wife?
别这样
Come on.
你拯救了一条生命
You saved a man's life.
彻底改变了他们错误的世界观
Course-corrected two peoples' wildly screwed-up world views.
对生活没坏处
It's not bad for a day's work.
他们以前是幸福的
I think they were happy.
即使是建立在谎言的基础
Even if it was based on lies.
大多数幸福都是这样
Most happiness is.
有性生活总比再也没有性生活好
Better to have schtupped and lost then never to have schtupped at all.
我们不能在这吸烟
We can't smoke in here.
我们还不能因为一个小小的赌注
We also can't summon people into the clinic
撒谎把人们叫到门诊呢
based on a lie motivated by a petty bet.
可我们还是这么做了啊
And yet it happens.
这是个不完美的世界
It's an imperfect world.
怎么样
Well?
令人恶心的满意
Disgustingly satisfying.
他说没事
He said it was okay.
你们谁是豪斯医生
Is one of you Dr. House?
看过斯巴达克斯吧
You've seen Spartacus, right?
我接到命令来拿掉电子脚镣
I got an order here to deactivate and remove his ankle monitor.
罗比吗
Robbie?
妹妹
Hi, sis.
多年不联系了
It's been years.
是的
I know.
妈妈生日那天  我想起了你
I thought of you on mom's birthday.
你没事吧
Is everything okay?
没事没事  我只是
Yeah, yeah. Fine. I just...
想知道你最近怎么样
Wanted to see how you were.
挺好的
I'm fine.
没有辅助轮  自行车会更快
Bikes go faster without training wheels.
出去  我还有事
Now get out. I have work to do.